wellplayed.org 2011-11-23

# Privacy Policy - Announcements - WellPlayed.org: Where eSports Lives

## Privacy Policy

  1. Preamble
  2. Our Principles
  3. Personal Information WP Collects
  4. What WP does with the Personal Information
  5. Disclosures of Personal Information
  6. Reorganization or Spin-Offs
  7. Children
  8. Third-Party Sites
  9. Special Note to International Users
  10. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy
  11. Attribution

This Master Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains the collection, use, and disclosure of “personal information” by WellPlayed Productions (“WP” or “WellPlayed”), a Delaware Limited Liability Company, through the website that WellPlayed operates at [http://WellPlayed.org](http://wellplayed.org/) (the “Website”). Furthermore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any of the websites operated by affiliates of WellPlayed.

This Privacy Policy also explains our commitment to you with respect to our use and disclosure of non personal browsing and site usage data that WellPlayed collects as the provider of the Website. 

As used in this policy, “personal information” means information that would allow a party to identify you including for example, but not limited to, your name, address or location, telephone number or email address.

By accessing the Website you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

WellPlayed is committed to handling responsibly the information and data we collect about you through our Website, whether personal information or non personal browsing and site usage data. We have designed our Privacy Policy consistent with the following principles (the “Principles”):

  * Privacy policies and data collection and use policies should be human readable, comprehensive, and easy to locate;

  * Only the minimum amount of information reasonably necessary to provide you with services should be collected and maintained, and only for so long as reasonably needed or required;

  * Information you provide through our Website, or that we gather as a result of your use of our Website, should not be used for marketing or advertising purposes, nor should it be provided voluntarily (without your permission) to anyone else unless required; and

  * Unless restricted or prohibited by law, and provided your email address has been collected and retained, you should be notified when circumstances require WellPlayed to provide a third party with your personal information.

We may collect personal information at several places on the Website, including without limitation:

  * when you provide us with your personal information such as by sending an email to us or signing up to receive a newsletter or our events listing;

  * when you subscribe to one of our email discussion lists or register to establish a user account on our Website

  * when you donate money to us or purchase merchandise;

  * when you join and when you thereafter create/edit your profile page, identify your content and/or share your story; and

• when you provide personal information in connection with your participation in any of the forums we make available to that community.

**Emails**. We use the personal information you provide to us when you send us emails in order to respond to your request — for example, to reply to your email or to send you communications about news and events related to WellPlayed.

**Password**. The Website does not store any plaintext passwords in our database. Nobody in WellPlayed, including but not limited to, our administrators and our moderators could ever possibly access your password. Since passwords are encrypted if you lose your password, we have to reset it. We respect your privacy and we do not store that information in any manner that can be retrieved by anyone in WellPlayed.

By joining the Website, you are also given a public profile page where you can voluntarily post personal information for public viewing. The information that you submit on your public profile page, including but not limited to information you provide in the field “About” and any photograph or image of yourself you upload, is posted by you at your discretion. The information you publish on your public profile page, including your personal information, may be used by anyone who views that information for any lawful purpose. WP may use the personal and non personal browsing information you provide in your public profile, including the text in the “About” field, to promote the mission of WellPlayed.

**Participating in Our Community** : Registered Users. When you register to obtain a user account on the Website you may be asked to provide personal information to create your account and establish a password and profile. Providing your email address and/or real name is optional. If you do provide your email address, it will allow us to send you your password if you should forget it. If you voluntarily provide your real name in connection with any content you submit to any Website, your name may be associated with the content you contributed. We will also use that personal information to establish and maintain your membership and provide you with the features we provide for Registered Users, and for the purpose of contacting you about upcoming news and events relevant to WellPlayed.

Any other personal information that we may collect which is not described specifically in this Privacy Policy will only be collected and used in accordance with the Principles.

In general, it is not WellPlayed’s practice to disclose personal information to third parties. We may share personal information in two instances: First, WellPlayed may share personal information with our contractors and service providers in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of the Website. Second, we may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; b) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or c) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.

If WellPlayed is required to provide a third party with your personal information (whether by subpoena or otherwise), then provided we have collected and retained an email address for you, WellPlayed will use reasonable means to notify you promptly of that event, unless prohibited by law or WP is otherwise advised not to notify you on the advice of legal counsel.

WellPlayed may transfer some or all of your personal and/or non personal browsing information to a third party as a result of a reorganization, spin-off or similar transaction. Upon such transfer, the acquirer’s privacy policy will apply. In such event, WellPlayed will use reasonable efforts to notify you and to ensure that at the time of the transaction the acquirer’s privacy policy complies with the Principles.

The Website is not directed at children under the age of 13. Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personal information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Our User Agreement specifically prohibits anyone using our Website from submitting any personally identifiable information about persons under 13 years of age. Any person who provides their personal information to WP through the Website represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

The Website may include links to other websites. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other websites.

The Website are hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions. By providing your personal data you consent to:

• the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and • the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the Effective Date below. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

This Privacy Policy is based in part on the Creative Commons Privacy Policy (<http://creativecommons.org/privacy).> You may use and share this template with anyone, free of charge, on the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License (<http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0).> However, in all cases, you must keep this notice (including the links) on copies or modified versions of the template, including on versions that you fill out for actual use as an agreement.

**Questions?**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [contact@wellplayed.org](mailto:contact@wellplayed.org).

**Effective Date: April 05, 2011**
